Hello, I'm from Ukraine, the city of
Здравствуйте я из Украины город
Khmelnitsk. You're
Хмельницк Вы
from near the city of
откуда рядом город
Ore, Moscow
Оре Московской
region,
обла
whatever your attitude to the war against
угодно как относитесь к войне против
Ukraine, to the war, it's bad, it
украины к войне плохо так
happened that it's cool to
случилось что так
observe the Minsk agreements, it's
сно минские соглашения соблюдать
cool to understand Tell me from your
прикольно понял Расскажите мне из своего
garage about the Minsk agreements, what was wrong with it,
гаража про минские соглашения что там не
read carefully Read  Well,
было прочитать внима Прочитайте Ну
Read Open, you can open it, I’ll open it
Прочитайте Откройте можете открыть ми я
and you Open it, let’s
открою и вы Откройте
read it Well, I
прочитаем Давайте слу Ну я примерно
had a dialogue like this about 850 times And I
такой диалог вёл примерно раз 850 А я
852 Let’s do it again now I’m
852 Давайте Вот мы сейчас ещё раз
a person with a legal
проведём Я человек с юридическим
education I like to discuss the Minsk
образованием Я люблю обсуждать минские
agreements Yes, if you have a legal
соглашения Да если вы с юридическим
education I think  that it is unlikely that you have a
образованием думаю что вряд ли вы с
legal education
юридическим образованием
takwa
таква
gender Read the Minsk
пол Прочитайте Минский
Protocol Minsk agreement 2 no two
протокол минские соглашение 2 нету два
or one there is no such document with
или один нету такого документа с
the name Minsk agreements one or the
названием минские соглашения один или
Minsk agreements WTO no no no look
мински соглашения ВТО не нету смотрите
no document with the name Minsk
нету документо с названием минские
agreements second or
соглашения вторые или
first Let's Open now there will be a
первые Давайте Открывайте сечас будет
prophecy of the witness of
пророчка свидетеля
Minsk  full
Минска полный
text read the title of the document we
текст зачитайте название документа мы
opened the
открыли один и тот
same document on a set of measures for the
же документ о комплексе мер по
implementation of agreements
выполнению соглашений
provided you are reading the original
предусмотрен вы читаете оригина
ichi
ичи
Oh so you opened a set of measures for the
О так вы вы открыли комплекс мер по
implementation of the Minsk agreements Open the
выполнению минских соглашений Откройте
Minsk
сами минские
agreements themselves before this the
соглашения до этого были подписаны
Minsk agreements were signed And this is a set of measures for
минские соглашения А это комплекс мер по
them  fulfillment
их выполнению
Yeah, let's do this and I have the text in
давайте так а мне са са текста в
the original
оригинале
Yes, in
Да в
Minsk I agreed with
мински согла
the document Minsk Protocol No, no, yes,
документо Минский протокол Нет не оно да
the protocol, yes, the protocol is called based on the
протокол да о называется протокол по
results of the consultation of the tripartite group,
итогам консультации трехсторонней группы
right here on the OS website I opened Let's get it
вот прямо на сайте обс Я открыл
right about yes, the
правильно про да
NKI agreement of
НКИ соглашение от
12 Read the title in  in the header of this
12 Прочитайте название в шапке этого
document, he said, find cash right away. So
документ ч сказал г найти сразу нал Так
you read, you know where he was, it was
вы читали вы знаете где он это было
so long ago already, you
настолько всё давно уже всё Вы же
said 812 times or
сказали 812 раз или
810 Let's
810 Давайте
Open September 5, 14 on the
Открывайте 5 сентября 14 года на сайте
OSCE website, enter
обсе вводишь
They are posted The OSCE was the guarantor between
Они же размещены обсе был гарантом между
Russia and Ukraine  therefore, on the OSCE website,
Россией и Украиной поэтому на сайте обсе
that
то
is, and the US was a guarantor, but well, the BS
есть а ус был гарантом да всё ну БС же
was not a party to the
не было стороной
conflict Well, a monitoring mission
конфликта Ну мониторинговый миссию Да
Yes, on the website the OSCE
так на сайте
Minsk Protocol Yes, the protocol Yes, the
быс Минский протокол Да протокол Да
Minsk Protocol
Минский протокол
Come on, based on the results of the consultation, a
Давай по итогам консультации
tripartite group, yes, yes, they opened in
трёхсторонняя группы да да открыли
September of the fourteenth year,
сентября четырнадцатого года
yes, Read the introduction  according to
Да так Прочитайте вступление по
the results, something needs to be opened,
результатам что-то надо его открыть ещё
wait a minute, but there’s a problem with opening documents
погоди а проблема с открытием документов
No, well, a certain level of education,
Нет ну определённый Уровень образования
for this you need to have documents,
для этого нужно иметь документы открывай
open them.
блин за минуту открыть докумен Слушай я
you understand yours, this is this
понимаю ты своё вот это вот это
Ukrainian brain catching Come on Find Find Find
украинско лов мозга Давай Находи Находи
open except for [ __ ] those
открыл кроме говна те
pain so the protocol of the reu third-party group
боль так протокол реу сторонней группы
Mins Chita trilateral contact
минс Чита трёхсторонняя контактная
group consisting of whom then consultations
группа в составе кого потом консультации
throne Gru joint steps forwarded by the
трон Гру совместных шагов
President of Ukraine Poroshenko
направ президент Украины Порошенко
initiatives of the President of Russia In Putin
инициативы Президента России В Путина
so Poroshenko and read  further on
так Порошенко и читай дальше по
the result of consideration of the
результата рассмотрение обсуждение
proposals of a hundred and
предложений ста и
read Ukraine of the Russian Federation of the
прочитай Украина Российской Федерации
organization of safe cooperation in
организации безопасно сотрудничества в
Europe reached an understanding sit out so that
Европе достигла понимание отсиди так то
is, look, the trilateral contact
есть смотрите трёхсторонняя контактная
group consisting of Ukraine, the Russian
группа в составе Украины Российской
Federation and the OSCE reached Okay, these three
Федерации и обсе достигла Окей эти три
parties Yes agreed For example, there
стороны Да договорились Вот например там
was a tenth point
был десятый пункт
Read those
Прочитайте вону тех
and mercenaries from the territory of Ukraine Russia
и наёмников с территории Украины Россия
has fulfilled this point; it has withdrawn illegally
выполнила этот пункт вывела незаконно
armed formations, military equipment
вооружённые формирования военную технику
and militants and mercenaries from the territory of
и боевиков и наёмников с территории
Ukraine. How can Russia
Украины Каким образом Россия может
withdraw if it signed this document?
вывести если она подписала Этот документ
Well, okay, it took upon itself to
что Ну хорошо она взяла на себя
withdraw once again and did not
обязательство вывести ещ раз и вывела не
withdraw. So wait how?  she brought it out
вводила Так подождите как она вывела
if there They
если там Они до сих
still mean for that no wait Wait Stop
пор значит для того нет погоди Подожди
You read it I I caught you look at the
Стоп Ты прочитал я Я тебя поймал смотри
tenth point says yes Russia
десятый пункт говорит да Россия
signed up to the obligatory withdrawal of
подписалась под обязательном вывести
illegal armed groups and
незаконные вооружённые формирования и
military equipment and Boyko mercenaries from the
военную технику и Бойко наёмников с
territory of Ukraine
территории Украины
signed I understood And that it did not withdraw  Yes, you are
подписала я понял И что не вывела Да ты
not a native lawyer, that is, you did not
не юрист родной для того то есть не
withdraw, that is, Russia did not comply with the
вывела то есть Россия не выполнила
Minsk
минские
agreements Russia did not fulfill the Minsk
соглашения Россия не выполнила минские
agreements, it fulfilled it 100% Well, how did it comply,
соглашения выполнила на 100% Ну как
it did not withdraw troops from the territory of
выполнила она не вывела войска с
Ukraine for a second, a
территории Украины секунду
second Find me where the monitoring
секунду Найди мне где мониторинговые
missions found at least one
миссии нашла хоть одни один раз
Russian ones  troops again, let me
российские войска ещё раз давай так я я
tell you now, yes Parla I’m telling you that
тебе сейчас да Парла Я говорю для то что
she started to introduce it and introduced it.
вывести она начала ввести она и вводила
Now I’m telling you right now I read you in
Сейчас я тебе сейчас я тебя пово говном
short about the Russian troops. And
короче по российским войскам прочитал А
you explain the tenth point, did Russia bring it out
ты объясни десятый пункт вывела Россия
or not? So she didn’t introduce it naturally
или нет Так она не вводила естественно
brought it out Of course, right away Well, in
вывела Конечно прямо сраз Ну по фак по
fact, in fact, signing because she didn’t enter it didn’t
факту подписание потому что не вводила
No, well, she didn’t enter it, but she
не Не ну как она она не вводила но
signed that she would bring it out, how does that
подписала что выведет как это так
mean Ukraine should have brought it out like
значит Украина должна была вывести как
Ukraine brought out a
Украина вывести
foreigner Rhone Russia Ukraine and both
иностра Роны Россия Украина и обе
excellent to should bring it out Russia don’t
отлично к должен выводить Россия не
wait
погоди
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
man and Ukraine Ukraine didn’t
человека у так и Украина Украина не
introduce how Ukraine should remove the deer from the
вводила как Украина должна вывести с
territory of
территории
Ukraine Read the fourth point And
Украины олень Прочитай четвёртый пункт А
listen, let’s run away now Yes,
слушай давай по ты сейчас убежишь Да
because I’ve already driven you into a corner,
потому что я тебя уже загнал в угол
read the fourth point Come on, I still have
читай четвёртый пункт Давай
n’t said anything yet
четв всех таки ещ ничего не сказал уже
all the permanent monitor whose
все постоянно действующий монито чей
nchi I read the protocol fourth point here
нчи читаю протокол четвёртый пункт вот
Let's ensure
Дава обеспечить
let's also deaf Yes you don't start to
давайс ещё и глухой Да ты не начинаешь
constantly ensure permanent
постоянно обеспечить постоянно
monitoring on the
действующий мониторинг на
Ukrainian-Russian state
украинско-российской государственной
border and verification of the OSCE country by
границе и верификацию страны обсе
creating a security zone in the
созданием зоны безопасности в
border areas of Ukraine Why
пограничных районах Украины Почему
why did they agree to provide
почему договаривались обеспечить
monitoring on the Ukrainian  The Russian border and it is
мониторинг на украино Российской грани и
safe for Ukraine and
безопасно Украиной и
Russia because they agreed between
Россией потому что договаривались между
Ukraine. And why? Well, that is, Ukraine and
Украиной А почему Ну то есть Украина с
Russia had something agreed to
Россией что-то имела договаривались
provide monitoring, provided
обеспечивать мониторинг обеспечивали
monitoring, monitoring and the creation of a
мониторинг мониторинг и создание зоны
security zone in the border regions of
безопасности в приграничных районах
Ukraine back in 20 years in the second year
Украины отда вышли 20 годов втором году
they came out before yes yes again  Look,
вышли пере да да ещё раз Смотри и
the creation of border
создание приграничных районах
security areas in the border regions of
безопасности в приграничных районах
Ukraine and the Russian Federation. So you read this with your
Украины и РФ Так ты это прочитал своими
lips, yes. And that Ukraine SRF would have
губами да А что у Украины срф бы было
something you read with your ass;
что-то ты жопой читал
Ukraine and the Russian Federation had
у Украины с Российской Федерацией были
some
какие-то
problems, I don’t know; Ukraine probably had
проблемы не знаю Украины наверное были
problems now. You  you asked you asked me
проблемы тепер Ты спрашивал ты просил
to tell you something on the OSCE website
чтобы я тебя на сайте обсе что-то сказал
yes Look, we’re opening it I’m now
да Вот смотри открываем Я сейчас на
opening it on the OSCE website so we’re writing it in the
обсе так открываем что пишем так в
search engine
поисковике
right away, so it means the 2015
сразу так значит набирает 2015 год
Helsinki Declaration of the OSCE
хельсинская декларация обсе
Parliamentary Assembly
парламентской Ассамблея
of the OSCE 15 Dasha Let me read it to
обсе 15 Даше Давай так я тебе прочитаю
you if  You won’t believe it
ты если не поверишь
naga Yes, come on, 2015, the Helsinki
нагу Да давай 2015 год хельсинская
Declaration Yes, here’s the first point, I think
декларация Да вот д первый пункт считаю
that the actions of the Russian Federation in the
что действия Российской Федерации в
Autonomous Republic of Crimea and in the city of
автономной республике Крым и в городе
Sevastopol, as well as in certain
Севастополе а также в определённых
areas of the Donetsk and Lugansk regions of
районах Донецкой и Луганской областей
Ukraine, are acts of military aggression
Украины являются актами военной агрессии
against Ukraine, there is a
против Украины есть
declaration, and the point calls on the Russian
декларация че пункт призывает Российскую
Federation  stop their campaign of
Федерацию прекратить свою компанию
destabilization in Ukraine, then escalate the
дестабилизации в Украине то эскалацию
conflict in certain areas of the
конфликта в определённых районах
Donetsk and Lugansk regions And in general
Донецкой и Луганской областей И вообще
completely withdraw from Ukraine, this is what the OSCE
полностью выйти из Украины это обсе
writes, they wrote so little. It
пишет они я так мало чего написал Оно же
didn’t introduce you understand. So no Missy No
не вводило понимаешь Так нет Мисси Нет
you said Find it, you said Show
ты сказал Находи давай ты сказал Покажи
me on the website  OSCE Find on the OSCE website the
мне на сайте обсе Находи на сайте обсе
Helsinki Declaration of the Parliamentary
хельсинская декларация парламентской
Assembly of the OSCE Let's open open don't
асамблея обсе Давай открой открывай не
let's read whose point let's look you
у давай зачитай чей пункт давай смотри
can
можно
point we can talk the twenty-fourth
пункт можно говорить двадцать четвёртый
point Read it don't say a Read it Just
пункт Зачитай не говори а Зачитай Просто
I'll wait Speak Read the two-
я подожду На говори Прочитай двад
fourth point Come on you can
четвёртый пункт Давай ты всё можно
read everything you opened the document  No,
прочитал ты открыл документ Нет ты
wait, you tell me, you opened the
погоди ты мне ты скажи ты открыл
Document and the destiny there is Russian. You
Документ и удел там российский Ты мне
show me the place, first of all, what did we go here, I tell
покажи место мы сначала что пошли вот я
you the OSCE on the basis of all the OSCE reports
вам го обсе на основании всех отчётов
And so on Yes, the
обсе И так дальше Да парламентская
OSCE Parliamentary Assembly made a resolution the OSCE
Ассамблея обсе сделала резолюцию отчёт
report where there is ys I tell you more  once I say
обс где есть йс я я тебе ещё раз говорю
Look calls Show me what OS where
Смотри призывает Покажи мне чтот обс где
there are Ukrainian troops What kind of nonsense There
есть украинские войска Что за бред Вот
is a parliamentary resolution, a resolution of the
есть парламентская резолюция резолюция
OSCE Parliamentary Assembly where they write clearly in
парламентской асамблея обсе где чётко
Cyrillic letters in Russian for
кириллические буквами русскими для
morons calls on the Russian
дебилов пишут призывает Российскую
Federation to stop its company,
Федерацию прекратить свою компанию всё
everything says that the occupier to withdraw troops from the
всё пишет что оккупант вывести войска из
Donetsk region, let's move on to 2017  year The
Донецкой области дальше берём 2017 год
Minsk Declaration, the resolution of the
Минская декларация резолюция
OSCE Parliamentary Assembly, from the first
парламентской Ассамблеи обсе со первый
paragraph, condemns numerous serious
пункт осуждает многочисленные серьёзные
cases of pressure of persecution and
случаи давления преследования и
intimidation of observers from the
запугивания наблюдателей из состава
special monitoring mission, along
специальной мониторинговой миссии наряду
with the case of deliberate destruction of
со случаем умышленного уничтожения
OSCE property in certain areas of the
имущества обсе в отдельных районах
Donetsk and Lugansk regions Where did you
донецко и луганских областей Куда ты
run away nit Yes Listen yes,
убежал гнида Да Слушай да находящихся
under the control of Russian hybrids  forces and
под контролем российских гибридных сил и
Urges the Russian
Настоятельно призывает Российскую
Federation to take practical measures to
Федерацию к принятию практических мер по
ensure proper conditions SM And so
обеспечению надлежащих условий SM И так
on Yes, and there are a lot of things like they
дальше Да и куча куча такого есть как их
really are bombed by [ __ ] fried the orc and so just
правда бомбит от [__] прожарил орка
2017 Minsk Declaration Yes, the
прос 2017 год Минская декларация Да
Parliamentary Assembly of the
парламентской Ассамблея
OSCE so condemn numerous seriously But
обсе так осуждать многочисленны серьёз А
this  it was not stop stop stop again it
вот это было было не стоп стоп стоп ещё
was
был
like this at once
так зараз
Here is the twelfth point in the resolution Yes
Вот вот в резолюции двенадцатый пункт Да
Taking into account the reports of the special
Принимая во внимание отчёты специального
monitoring mission of the OSCE SMM That is,
мониторинговой миссии смм обсе То есть
those reports that you referred to yes
те отчёты на которые ты арче ссылался да
in Ukraine about a large accumulation of heavy
в Украине о большом скоплении тяжёлых
weapons of modern types of military
вооружений современных видов военной
equipment in  including those in
техники в том числе состоящих на
service with the Russian Armed
вооружении тельно российских Вооружённых
Forces in certain areas of the Donetsk and
сил в отдельных районах Донецкой и
Lugansk regions of Ukraine
Луганской областей Украины
not controlled by the government of Ukraine,
неподконтрольных правительству Украины
including areas in which the presence of
включая районы в которых присутствие
heavy weapons is prohibited by the Minsk
тяжёлых вооружений запрещено минскими
agreements. The resolution of the
соглашениями в в резолюция парламентской
OSCE Parliamentary Assembly, referring to the reports of the
Ассамблеи обсе ссылаясь на отчёты
daily special monitoring
ежедневной специальной мониторинговой
mission of the OSCE, directly states that
миссии обсе прямо говорится Да что
Russian equipment  are present in
российская техника присутствуют в
certain areas of the Luhansk and Donetsk
отдельных районах Луганской и Донецкой
regions and all these that open the
области и вот все эти которые открывают
Ro-Minsk agreements Yes, when
ро про минские соглашения Да когда с
you take them and so you start point by point
ними берёшь и так начинаешь по пунктах
Here they are, somehow a hunted rat begins to
Вот они как-то загнанная крыса начинает
run away they have a lucky
убегать у них есть счастливая такая
button like this further He ran away and went to [ __ ]
кнопочка далее Он убежал и пошёл [__]
on others  in the brains therefore Who
другим в мозги поэтому Кто в Российской
opens the race in the Russian Federation Yes and says that
Федерации открывает род Да и говорит что
Minsk and Ukraine did not comply Yes these are all
Минск и Украина не исполняла Да это всё
complete Russians Yes they support
конченные Раши сы Да они поддерживают
the occupation of Ukraine under just
оккупацию Украины под просто предлогом
such an excuse Yes they need an excuse to
таким Да им нужен предлог чтобы
justify theirs
оправдать свою
Like this And we will fry everyone and
Вот так А мы будем жарить каждого
distribute this video  to their friends,
распространять это видео своим друзьям
let them understand the Armed Forces more and
да пусть они разбираются ВС больше и
understand what a [ __ ] Putin is, and the
понимают какой Путин говнюк да И
majority of the population of the Russian
большинство населения Российской
Federation are such complete imperials.
Федерации вот такие конченые имперцы
Glory to Ukraine and try the ZS letter on the
Слава Украине и тримайте ЗС пись на й
Telegram right now, the axis of the VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apoc tse more and more politely YouTube is
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through Scar Geor into the shadows  ban
загоняет нас через Скар Геор в теней бан
and even more rich video I don’t show people
и дуже багато вдео не показую людям
at the moment I don’t show information about the stream
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
For this purpose, we need to write a Mali operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link right away and while there in the
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm video schezh Tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are sorry for you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
regardless of that  I will show you the process
незалежно в того покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukrai
YouTube Слава украи
shi
ши